You didn't wash the meat.
I didn't wash the meat!
Stop it!
Hello!
We are the Iginari Corps.
Yes!
You look down today.
I'm down.
We haven't had lunch yet.
So, we want you to make lunch.
I see.
Today, we will have a cooking relay.
Is it a relay?
What is it?
First, there are 6 of us today, so
please divide into 2-2-2.
There are 2 teams to buy food, 2 teams
to prepare the ingredients, and 2 teams
to cook.
We will have a relay for 20 minutes
each.
What?
Isn't it short?
I thought it was 90 minutes.
So, we will announce the dishes you
will make today.
Who will it be?
What will it be?
The dish you will make today is
Okuzuka.
What is it?
Do you know what it is?
I thought you would say that.
So, I chose Okuzuka today.
Have you ever made Okuzuka?
I haven't.
Isn't it a dish you eat together?
Yasumura, you should shut up.
Shut up!
As I said, there are 3 teams, so if you
know the ingredients, you don't have to
make it.
I see.
So, you have to decide what you will
make.
But, I didn't know Okuzuka when I went
to buy it.
What did you buy?
You will make dishes with 6 people, so
you will divide into teams.
Let's divide into teams.
What is that?
But, it should be a group.
I think it's a group.
You will be on the side, but you will
be on the representative team.
The team who buys the ingredients, the
team who prepares the ingredients, and
the team who cooks will be on the
winning team.
Rock-paper-scissors.
You are the winner.
I won.
I'm not good at playing rock-paper-
scissors.
I won.
Kani and Hazuki will buy the
ingredients.
Kizaki and Date will prepare the
I'll prepare the ingredients.
Finally, Kichise and Yasunori will
cook.
We have decided the teams, so let's go
to buy the ingredients.
Let's go.
Let's go to buy the ingredients.
We have come to buy the ingredients.
It's sunny.
We will go to Espar to buy the
ingredients.
We have a good team.
That's right.
It's not good.
We have decided the team, not the team.
That's right.
It's not our intention.
There are many shops, so please buy the
ingredients you need.
Unfortunately, we don't allow you to
shoot.
That's right.
We are waiting for you, so please buy
the ingredients.
I understand.
I will buy a lot of sweets that look
delicious.
That's great.
If you can buy the ingredients,
anything is fine.
That's right.
We don't know the legend, so we will
buy the ingredients.
You two are the team to procure the
ingredients.
Please look at the ingredients and
decide what the other two teams will
make.
We will do our best.
Please make it well.
They have bought the ingredients.
Please subscribe to the channel.
I bought it
Ta-da
I will introduce the purchased goods
First of all, this is water
Oil
Dashi
White Dashi
You can use it for anything
Soy sauce
Yes, it's important
Caramel
Egg
Salt, it's seasoned salt
Chicken breast
Flour
What is that?
It's for eating
Snacks
I can't do without these
Our partner
Kinoya Ishinomaki Suisan's
Ginkasa
Cucumber
But this is
Different purpose
I bought it because I wanted you to
make Asazuki
I will put it in the set
Deep-fried tofu
Potato starch
And potato for potato starch
Eggplant
Bonito
Escher lettuce
What is this?
It's okay
That's all
It seems difficult to cook from here
It's not for you and me
I bought it because I thought it was
for anything
I like it
Next, we will prepare for the base
Good luck
Please subscribe to our channel
The next day
We are the studio team
I'm Toka
I'm Tomo
What was that?
Thank you for watching!
Thank you very much.
You are welcome.
We have a cooking team.
So, you should prepare for the cooking
team.
I can't eat this.
You should prepare for the cooking
team.
First, imagine what you are going to
cook.
Then, prepare for the cooking team.
You have 20 minutes.
20 minutes?
I will wash my hands.
Don't count the time.
I didn't say let's go.
Let's go.
Wash your hands.
You have 20 minutes.
Get ready.
Do I open this?
It's difficult.
I should cut this.
Which channel is this?
It's Nishinomoto.
It's Kana.
I noticed it.
It's not Kinkasaba.
I'll do it.
Stop advertising.
Kinkasaba.
Please subscribe to this channel.
What are you doing?
I like cabbage.
Which one is lettuce?
I don't like cabbage.
You like cabbage?
I like cabbage.
I'll eat it.
How many minutes left?
I don't know.
You didn't wash the meat.
I didn't wash the meat.
Stop it.
I'm serious.
I'm not interested in meat.
We just started to cut the meat.
10 minutes left.
Don't worry.
We have 2 songs left.
How can I cut it?
I'll cut it.
The cheering squad is here.
What are they?
What are you making?
It looks like a dish.
Is there anyone who is eating?
I think there is someone who is eating.
I'm eating alone.
Is it related to the dish?
The dish?
Can I peel it?
No.
I made it with fresh fish.
I made it.
What is it?
Fresh fish.
I made meat.
Do you put the seasoning on the meat?
I put it in the soup.
I see.
It's curry.
Is it curry?
I should put it on eggplant.
It's fun.
Did you put it in there?
Which one?
Both?
It's curry.
It's getting delicious.
It's getting hot.
I'm done.
What kind of dish is it?
I thought it was a stylish dish.
So, I thought it was a stylish dish.
I thought it was a dish that I was
rolling.
I see.
It's a pot rather than a frying pan.
I don't know.
I'll leave it to the staff.
Yes.
Thank you for watching this video.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Yeah!
We grew up so much since the seventh
grade!
It's an opportunity just for us!
I got in a army, with Mr. Gassan.
Gassan?
I was playing the role of Yukina, and
some 톰 I just knew
Nikumo輸通生
I had started practicing JAFT
What is this used for?
Is this meat?
This is meat
Bye!
What did you put on it?
I put on the seasoning.
I wonder what you put on it.
That's why the soup stock is gone.
I can't get the soup stock.
I'm angry.
You have 20 minutes.
Yes.
Ready, start.
What are you going to do?
What are you going to do with the
eggplant?
I don't need it.
But,
I think there is a potato in it.
Then,
I'll put it instead of the potato.
Can you do it?
I'll put everything in it.
It's a vegetable, so it's OK.
Is it OK to put a big one?
What?
Everything is fine.
She is just putting it back again and
again.
I'm going to put it back.
Is it OK if it's not hot?
What? Is it OK?
Where is the can of that can?
I see.
It's from KINAYA.
Thank you.
It's got tamarind.
I thought it had an orange color.
I'll put it in.
Do you put it in?
It's a lot.
I think so.
What is this?
Is it a food?
It's a decoration.
It's a white food.
It's really big.
It's amazing.
It's a big enough to eat a hippo.
I'll put this in.
I'll put fried tofu in.
Do you wanna taste it?
I'm not good at hot food.
I'll taste it.
I'll put fried tofu in.
This face is terrible.
This is not bad.
I can eat this.
But, I think it's better to add more
flavor.
Do you get rid of the bad taste?
No.
I don't get rid of the bad taste.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I'm going to do it.
Udon.
You're right.
It's good.
Really?
It's good?
It's a soup stock.
It's OK.
It's perfect.
It's done.
The second dish, Okuzukake, is done.
I did my best.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Each team has created a puzzle and did
various things.
Let's ask each team what they were
imagining.
Let's start with the team who bought
it.
I imagined something like a bean paste.
That's why there was a lot of potato
starch.
And if it fails, it will be made into a
thick paste.
I was worried if I would use all the
potato starch.
We were different.
I imagined something like a potato
paste.
I imagined something like a soup of
boiled down.
I imagined chicken.
I imagined chicken and flowers.
I imagined a Western-style dish.
I imagined curry.
I imagined a soup of boiled down.
The team who bought it is correct.
What was it?
I put something in it.
Do you want to put it in?
I can eat it.
Please subscribe to this channel.
It's good!
It's a joke!
Let's eat!
It's good!
Our white soup stock was effective.
Chicken soup stock was effective.
I thought we were going to make
something weird.
I added some elements that can make
What is this?
I know you don't use this or turmeric,
but I brought it.
It was good.
I think we can eat only chicken.
It's like a baby's mother.
It's the size of a giraffe or a hippo.
It's like a female eggplant.
I cut eggplant in half.
It's like a cream puff.
You ate all of them.
That's amazing.
We ate them all.
You ate the flowers.
I ate them.
Did you?
How was it?
It was like a baby's mother.
I ate this one.
It's like a flower.
You did.
You did well this time, so please try
to make a dish that you can't make.
We don't say that we failed.
We're going to finish shooting and eat
the rest.
Thank you for the meal.
Thank you for watching this video.
Please subscribe to this channel.